First T-virus malware in history
to target
Iran's nuclear program.  It was just
proof that you can actually do damage to
software.  It
's been 6-7 months since we started and
then Enel tried the product and
started wanting it, right?  He wanted to
give it back to us, but when there is
exponential growth, maybe the following year
a few tens of thousands of euros,
a few hundred, up to ok
million, 2 million 10. The
startup book says you have to aim for the PO and
to get there you have to grow
significantly.  You can't just sit back and
grow your business organically
because others are playing that game.
We are still the only player in our
market that Espositi, that is, all the
others, are losing.
You may not know his name,
yet every government knows his
company.  He is Morano Carullo, born in 1982
and together with Andrea Carcano in 2013 he
founded Nozomi Networks which deals with
protecting the
most sensitive infrastructures from hackers.  of the
most powerful countries in the world, power grids,
airports, military facilities, even
the Super Bowl.  In short, it
deals with industrial cyber security and
starting from Italy, Nozomi has arrived
all the way to Silicon Valley, raising
over 260 million dollars, before
being acquired for 1 billion by
Mitsubishi in 2025, becoming one of the
largest investments in the world in
this sector.  And that's why I went to
Nozomi's headquarters in Switzerland to
talk to Moreno.